ANTONIS MITOS KOTSIS

• DETAILS •

Préveza Greece +306947374921

AntonisKotsis@protonmail.com

SKILLS

Java

Python

Node.js

JavaScript

SQL

MonogDB

React.js

HTML & CSS

Data Structures

Complex Problem Solving

• HOBBIES •

Basketball, Travelling

• LANGUAGES •

Greek

English

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

Portfolio

PROFILE

A certified Software Engineer specializing in Android and web applications. Over my university years at UOI, Object-Oriented Programming and Algorithm's Efficiency got my attention. Since then, I've worked on many projects as a freelancer. Recently, I finished my duty at the Greek Army as a Private Software Developer contributing code and maintaining web apps. I also received a Letter of Recommendation from the Greek Army due to my excellent performance and work ethic under stressful situations. Now I'm studying the MERN stack, so I can expand my knowledge to the web applications field. Using the above technical skill set combined with my problem-solving and fast learning abilities as well as team player attitude and my constant need to accomplish the highest standards, I am able to add value and contribute to the company's achievements where I'll work.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer at Greek Army, Alexandroupolis, GR

November 2021 — August 2022

- Built, deployed and maintained web features using mostly the MERN stack.
- Development of Desktop applications deployed in Linux machines, using Java 11 and JavaFX.
- Contributed to the implementation of a data analysis and visualization application using Python 3.

Software Developer at Steve Coffee Shop, Preveza, GR

June 2019 — August 2021

- Implemented a Portable order system Android application using Java.
- Created and maintained their promotion website using Python and Django.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science and Engineering, University of Ioannina, Ioannina, GR September 2015 — September 2020

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering, Univesity of Ioannina, Ioannina, GR September 2015 — September 2019

COURSES

Data structures and Algoriths efficiency, Udemy

March 2022 — May 2022

Fullstack Developer Roadmap, Udemy

December 2021 — April 2022